A Guide to the Robert T. Muse Papers, 1958-2014
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Robert T. Muse Papers, 1958-2014
The Library of Virginia
51335
20.475 cubic feet (45 boxes).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Robert T. Muse, Aberdeen, Maryland.
Biographical Information
Robert Thaddeus Muse, Sr. was born in Dillonvale, Ohio on 2 October 1925. He is the son of Thaddeus Hatcher Muse (1892-1973) and Anna Webster (1893-1981). The family moved to Canton, Ohio in 1937. Muse attended Virginia Tech from 1942 to 1943, and then enlisted in the United States Navy during World War II. After the war, he resided in Petersburg, Virginia, and then returned to Virginia Tech, where he received a degree in industrial physics. From 1951 to 1962, Muse was employed by Titmus Optical Company in Petersburg. He then was a physicist at Fort Lee until 1973. Muse was transferred to the Aberdeen Proving Ground in Maryland in 1973, and retired there in 1985. He married 1) Ann Elizabeth Brookes (1920-1980) on 22 June 1947, and 2) Betty Mae (Monroe) Meister (1922-2011) on 17 September 1988. Muse died 8 August 2018 in Aberdeen, Maryland, and was buried in Southlawn Memorial Cemetery in Petersburg, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1958-2014, of Robert T. Muse (1925-2018) of Aberdeen, Maryland, containing his genealogical research on the Muse family, notably the descendants of John Muse, Sr. (1633-1723) of Souldrop, Bedfordshire, England, and Westmoreland County, Virginia. Most of the files relate to his service as historian for the Muse Reunion Association. The collection includes family group sheets, research/source files, and indexes.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Family Group Sheets.
Series II. Research/Source Files.
Series III. Indexes.
Contents List
- Series I. Family Group Sheets., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 1-9)
  There are approximately 8800 family group sheets that were originally housed in three-ring binders. The largest portion of these relate to the descendants of John Muse, Sr. There are also sheets on nine other Muse lineages. The "identity code" located in the upper right portion of each sheet establishes the generation for each individual and the issue number of that individual for the parents' children. Letters indicate the generation, and numbers indicate the issue of the parents. An explanation of the identity code system used by Muse is located in the first folder of the collection. A complete set of the family group sheets are contained on DVD at the end of the series. In addition, there are "sources of information" codes at the bottom of each family group sheet which indicate the research source for the information Muse used. The research/source files are contained in Series II. There is an index to the family group sheets arranged alphabetically by name in Series III.
  - Identity Code Explanation. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Binder #1 J1 - J1K2L2M1N4O1P8. (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Binder #2 J1K2L2M1N4O2P1 - J1K2L2M3N9O7P9. (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Binder #3 J1K2L2M1N1O1P1Q1 - J1K2L2M1N10O4P1Q7. (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
  - Binder #4 J1K2L2M1N10O4P3Q1 - J1K2L2M1N1O1P1Q7R1. (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Binder #5 J1K2L2M1N1O3P1Q1R1 - J1K2L2M1N4O2P8Q1R2. (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Binder #5A J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P4Q6R4. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Binder #6 J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R1 - J1K2L2M3N1O4P4Q1R2. (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
  - Binder #7 J1K2L2M3N1O5P1Q1R2 - J1K2L2M3N5O4P12Q3R9. (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Binder #8 J1K2L2M3N5O4P12Q7R1 - J1K2L2M3N9O4P4Q11R6. (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Binder #8A J1K2L2M1N1O1P1Q1R1S1 - J1K2L2M1N4O1P1Q5R3S4. (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
  - Binder #9 J1K2L2M1N4O1P1Q5R4S1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q3R2S5. (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Binder #9A J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q3R3S1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R9S10. (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Binder #10 J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R10S1 - J1K2L2M1N4O7P1Q2R4S3. (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
  - Binder #10A J1K2L2M1N4O7P1Q2R6S1 - J1K2L2M3N4O9P2Q6R1S4. (Box 3, Folder 10-12)
  - Binder #11 J1K2L2M3N4O9P2Q6R2S1 - J1K2L2M3N9O4P4Q10R8S3. (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - Binder #12 J1K2L2M1N1O1P1Q1R1S3T3 - J1K2L2M1N4O1P1Q5R9S5T4. (Box 4, Folder 4-6)
  - Binder #12A J1K2L2M1N4O1P1Q6R1S1T1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R2S8T7. (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Binder #13 J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R3S1T1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P3Q5R9S2T5. (Box 4, Folder 9-11)
  - Binder #13A J1K2L2M1N4O5P4Q3R1S1T1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R5S6T3. (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Binder #13AA J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R6S1T1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q4R5S1T1. (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - Binder #14 J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q5R1S9T1 - J1K2L2M1N4O7P1Q2R2S1T5. (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
  - Binder #14A J1K2L2M1N4O7P1Q2R3S1T1 - J1K2L2M3N4O9P2Q9R10S7T15. (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
  - Binder #15 J1K2L2M3N5O3P3Q7R5S3T1 - J1K2L2M3N9O4P1Q3R1S6T5. (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
  - Binder #15A J1K2L2M3N9O4P2Q1R3S1T3 - J1K2L2M1N1O6P4Q5R5S3T2U3. (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Binder #15B J1K2L2M1N1O6P4Q5R5S4T1U1 - J1K2L2M1N4O1P4Q6R11S5T5U2. (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - Binder #16 J1K2L2M1N4O1P4Q6R11S6T2U1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R7S2T6U4. (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Binder #17 J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R7S2T7U1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q3R6S4T7U4. (Box 6, Folder 8-10)
  - Binder #17A J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q9R1S3T2U2 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R11S4T5U4. (Box 6, Folder 11-13)
  - Binder #17B J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R11S4T7U1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q5R4S2T8U3. (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Binder #17C J1K2L2M1M4O5P7Q7R1S1T11U1 - J1K2L2M1N4O6P1Q1R1S3T2U12. (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Binder #17D J1K2L2M1N4O6P1Q1R2S3T1U1 - J1K2L2M3N5O4P10Q1R1S2T2U7. (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
  - Binder #18 J1K2L2M3N5O4P10Q1R1S2T3U1 - J1K2L2M1N1O3P1Q7R3S4T2U7V3. (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
  - Binder #19 J1K2L2M1N1O3P1Q7R3S4T2U10V1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R1S9T3U1V1. (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  - Binder #19A J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R1S9T3U2V1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q3R5S1T6U8V1. (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Binder #19B J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q3R5S1T6U9V1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P10Q1R8S5T10U4V2. (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Binder #19C J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q1R6S1T2U1V1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q5R3S10T6U4V1. (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Binder #19D J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q5R3S10T6U4V2 - J1K2L2M3N4O9P2Q9R8S5T1U1V5. (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - Binder #20 J1K2L2M3N4O9P2Q9R10S7T3U3V1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R1S9T5U2V1W4. (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
  - Binder #21 J1K2L2M1N4O5P1Q1R1S9T5U2V2W1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q5R3S3T3U2V2W2. (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Binder #22 J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q5R3S3T6U2V1W1 - J1K2L2M1N4O5P7Q3R2S2T1U6V3W2X1. (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Family Group Sheets on DVD. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Series II. Research/Source Files., Extent: 34 boxes. (Box 9-43)
  The research/source files include the information used to compile the family group sheets, and also in Muse's collaboration with Dr. Roger David Chambers and Lou Andrews Murphy on "A Southern Legacy: Descendants of John Muse of Virginia - Volumes I and II," which were issued in 1994 and 1997. The files contain abstracts, copies, and transcriptions of deeds, census records, church records, land patents and grants, military and pension records, tax records, vital statistics, and wills, as well as Bible records and family registers, clippings, correspondence, family group sheets, genealogical charts and pedigrees, obituaries and epitaphs, photographs, and information from published sources. The material in the research/source files was obtained by Muse on various research trips around the country, and from other Muse family members and researchers. There are inquiries regarding specific ancestors or lines of descent from individuals he met at annual Muse family reunions who were seeking to exchange information, and responses to inquiries that were published in "Everton's Genealogical Helper" by Muse and others. The files are arranged alphabetically by research/source code, and there are duplicate codes for some of the folders. There is an index to these files in Series III.
  - A-C "The Muse (Mewes) Family of the Northern Neck of Virginia" by Mary N. West and Juliet Fauntleroy - Virginia Magazine of History and Biography (1945). (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - D Hopkins of Virginia and Related Families by Walter Lee Hopkins (1931). (Box 9, Folder n/a)
  - E "A Compilation of Genealogical Data on the Muse Family by E. W. McDonald, Orlando FL" (1971). (Box 10, Folder n/a)
  - F Notes. (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
  - F-8 William Travers Muse. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - F-I Ruby Moser (Charlotte NC). (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - F-J Northern Neck Cemeteries. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - F-K Virginia Parishes. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - F-L Charles E. Muse Jr. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - F:L-1. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - F:L-1. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:N Maryann Stalpers. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - F:O Blacksburg Library. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - F:P Rev. Roger Hudson. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - F:Q Leonard G. Muse. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - F:R Ruby B. Clayson. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - F:S Scotland. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - F:T 1980 Leesburg Trip (Lawrence Muse). (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - F:V Hazel McCarthy McDonald. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - F:W MatLee Benton Cathey. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - F:W Mrs. Harry Goodwin Muse (Washington's Birthplace VA). (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - F:X Rebecca Muse Gunter. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - F:Y James H. Womack (Charlotte NC). (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - F:Y James H. Womack (Charlotte NC). (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:Z Arthur Muse Waldrop (Jacksonville FL). (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - F:BB. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - F:CC Adeline Muse - Key West FL (Eastern NC Information). (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
  - F:CC Adeline Muse - Key West FL (Eastern NC Information). (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:CC Blacksburg Library. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - F:DD Jessie Muse Bastin. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - F:EE John C. Muse. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - F:FF William T. Owens-Smith (Bethesda MD). (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - F:FF Ila Hughes - Villa Grove IL (Pulaski KY Muses). (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - F:GG Dorrine V. Koch. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - F:HH 1980 Muse Reunion Registrations. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - F:HH Betty and Jim Muse (Mt. Gilead NC). (Box 12, Folder 5-8)
  - F:HH Betty and Jim Muse (Mt. Gilead NC). (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:II Richard Muse Book (portion). (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - F:II Richard Muse (Georgetown KY). (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - F:II Richard Muse (Georgetown KY) (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:JJ Hazel Buno. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - F:LL Delsie Olita Tomblin Beard. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - F:MM Frank J. Lokey. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - F:NN Travers Muse (Baltimore MD). (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - F:OO Edna B. Prokop. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - F:PP Chambers, Dr. Roger David. (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
  - F:PP Chambers, Dr. Roger David. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:PP Chambers, Dr. Roger David. (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - F:PP-2 David Chambers. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - F:QQ Mrs. James B. Marbert. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - F:RR Mrs. Judy Estep. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - F:SS Ann Stokes. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - F:TT Trudie Davis Long. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - F:VV Riley C. Fields. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - F:WW Al Fulton. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - F:WW Robert Eugene Muse. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - F:XX Mrs. James W. Campbell. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - F:YY Mrs. H.R. Ball (Helen). (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - F:ZZ Lloyd R. Barnwell. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - F:AAA Mary Jo Abbott Everett. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - F:BBB Mrs. Adine C. Owen. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - F:CCC Linda Patton. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - F:DDD John Boogaerts. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - F:EEE Mrs. Milton E. Adams (Carol). (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - F:FFF Jerry Ray Smith. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - F:GGG Raymond I. Muse. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - F:HHH Mrs. Pat Barker (Mary). (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - F:III Mrs. Paul L. Adamson. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - F:JJJ Carthage NC Cemeteries. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - F:KKK Donald F. Muse (Santa Clara CA). (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - F:LLL San Jose CA. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - F:MMM Mrs. Lou Murphy. (Box 14, Folder 1-12)
  - F:MMM Mrs. Lou Murphy. (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
  - "A Study of Lt. Col. George Muse (1720-1790) by Lou Andrews Murphy. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "Louisiana Muses: Daniel, James H., Thomas J." by Lou A. Murphy. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Lt. Col. George Muse Except Who His Parents Were" by Lou A. Murphy. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - F:NNN Delbert Frank Muse (Poulsbo WA). (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  - F:OOO Mrs. H.G. Lacy. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - F:PPP Mrs. Aline Metcalf. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - F:QQQ Wesley Caviness. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - F:RRR Mr. Marion E. Muse. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - F:SSS Cathy C. Moore. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - F:TTT Edgar C. Muse Sr. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - F:VVV Cecil R. Humphery-Smith (England). (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - F:WWW Mrs. A.R. Bigwood (Scotland). (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - F:WWW Mrs. Jeanette Borland. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - F:XXX Lois Culver. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - F:YYY Andrew W. Buck (Betha Muse, Brooklyn NY). (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - F:ZZZ Lamar Muse (Dallas TX). (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - F:AAAA Florence Muse (Brawley CA). (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - F:BBBB Kathleen C. Kelly. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - F:CCCC Walter B. Muse Jr. (Ypsilanti MI). (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - F:DDDD Pearl E. (Muse) Fitzgerald (Pulaski TN). (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - F:EEEE Emma Gene Gentry (Austin TX). (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - F:FFFF James A. Muse Sr. (Nashville TN). (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - F:GGGG Edward Napier (Falls Church VA). (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - F:HHHH George G. Muse (Johnson City NC). (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - F:IIII Mrs. Robert L. Jones (Norwich OH). (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - F:JJJJ Irene Muse Miller. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - F:KKKK Louise Taylor Muse (Columbia MD). (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - F:LLLL Mrs. Claude Revere Muse (Charlotte NC). (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - F:MMMM Jeanette Muse Colvin (Newellton LA). (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - F:NNNN Mrs. Elveda Starkey. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - F:OOOO Ruth Sanford (Indianapolis IN). (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - F:PPPP Mrs. Raymond Muse (New Concord OH). (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - F:QQQQ Robert Lee Muse. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - F:RRRR William Scott Muse (Knoxville TN). (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - F:SSSS Carolyn and Don Muse (Hampton VA). (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - F:SSSS-2 Caroline Muse (Johnson City TN). (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - F:TTTT Dorothy Irvin. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - F:VVVV James R. Muse (Leesburg VA). (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - F:WWWW Rev. Charlie M. Muse. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - F:WWWW Eunice Barrow (San Antonio TX). (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - F:XXXX Paul F. Muse (Terre Haute IN). (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - F:YYYY McIner Family of North Carolina. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - F:ZZZZ Margie Muse Meister. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - F:AAAAA Martha Twitchell Muse. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - F:BBBBB Juliet Fauntleroy Papers - UVA. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - F:CCCCC Mrs. Jacques Kelly (Washington DC). (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - F:DDDDD Dorothy Myer (Victoria TX). (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - F:EEEEE Alicia A. McShulkis (Maple Shade NJ). (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - F:FFFFF Pearl B. Fry (Carthage NC). (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - F:GGGGG South Carolina Archives/USC Library. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - F:HHHHH D. Morton Rose. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - F:IIIII Betty Muse Prouty (Jupiter FL). (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - F:JJJJJ Mrs. Elton Thompson (Roslyn Muse) Tullahoma TN. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - F:KKKKK E.W. McDonald (Orlando FL). (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - F:LLLLL Willie Rae Muse (Jackson MS). (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - F:MMMMM J. Daniel Muse (Tullahoma TN). (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - F:NNNNN Paul A. Muse (Memphis TN). (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - F:OOOOO 1986 Southeastern States Trip. (Box 17, Folder 21-22)
  - F:PPPPP Mrs. E.B. Brockenbrough (Waco TX). (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - F:QQQQQ Leon R. Barnwell (Eugene OR). (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - F:RRRRR Ruthe Muench (Tampa FL). (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - F:SSSSS Gaylia A. Burdick (Mexico MO). (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - F:TTTTT Janice Muse Frye. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - F:UUUUU Barbara Knott Horsman (Chantilly VA). (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - F:VVVVV Paul Muse (Suffolk VA). (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - F:WWWWW Thyra Fager (Abilene KS). (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - F:XXXXX Lori Foster Crow (Athens GA). (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - F:YYYYY Mrs. Reid D. Farrell (Sarasota FL). (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - F:ZZZZZ Don Muse (Washington DC). (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - F:AB Mrs. Allen N. Sweeny (Osterville MA). (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - F:AD Kim R. Mathena (Montgomery IL). (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - F:AE Frances B. Burrows (Tucson AZ). (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - F:AF Jean Bigger (Tullahoma TN). (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - F:AG Margaret Ellen Muse Jackson (Memphis TN). (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - F:AH Christine Nelson (Corinth MS). (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - F:AI Ann Thomason (Bloomington TX). (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - F:AJ Edward C. Muse (Dallas TX). (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - F:AK Walker Muse. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - F:AL James Clarence Muse III (Dallas TX). (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - F:AM Mrs. Fred Edgemon (Sweetwater TN). (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - F:AN Mildred Peak (Fort Smith AR). (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - F:AO Carolyn Ryan (Akron OH). (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - F:AP Vernon R. Muse (Manchester CT). (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - F:AQ Mountain View Cemetery (Vinton VA)/Blacksburg Library. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - F:AR Robert H. Muse (Orlando FL). (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - F:AS Joe Hamner Muse (Blue Ridge VA). (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - F:AT William Van Muse (Akron OH). (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - F:AV Mrs. Joe Muse (Terlton OK). (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - F:AW Nancy Seawell Brown (Durango CO). (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - F:AX Jessie M. Von Eschen (West Columbia SC). (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - F:AY Mina Ruth Muse (South Jordan UT). (Box 18, Folder 30-32)
  - F:AY Mina Ruth Muse (South Jordan UT). (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:AZ Julia Aitken (West Helena AR). (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - F:AZA Cecil Muse (Dundalk MD). (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - F:AZB Mrs. Durward W. Morgan (Ripley MS). (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - F:AZC Walter Muse (Union City TN). (Box 19, Folder 3a)
  - F:AZD June 1987 Oklahoma and Kentucky Trip. (Box 19, Folder 4-6)
  - F:AZD-2 Eunice Muse Smith (Austin TX). (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - F:AZE Fred Muse (Heavener OK). (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - F:AZF Hershel W. Muse (Tulsa OK). (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - F:AZG Hestel Muse Johnston (Tennille GA). (Box 19, Folder 10-15)
  - F:AZG-2 Hestel Muse Johnston (Tennille GA). (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
  - F:AZI Lewis Frederick (Cabool MO). (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - F:AZJ VaLera Muse Lewis (Knoxville TN). (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - F:AZK Daniel and Alice Muse (Oklahoma City OK). (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - F:AZL Eddie and Weta Muse Womack (Wilburton OK). (Box 20, Folder 10-12)
  - F:AZM Herbert Anderson (Edmonton KY). (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - F:AZN Zena Frederick (Coalgate OK). (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - F:AZO Margaret Smith (Houston AL). (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - F:AZP Barbara Clepper (Sheffield AL). (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - F:AZQ Allen W. Post Jr. (Atlanta GA). (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - F:AZR Mrs. William Glenn Post Jr. (St. Petersburg FL). (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - F:AZS Eleanor Thomas (Kenneth City FL). (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - F:AZT Jay Muse (Heavener OK). (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - F:AZV Mrs. Louise Hagwood (Clarksdale MS). (Box 21, Folder 1-6)
  - F:AZV-2 Mrs. Louise Hagwood (Clarksdale MS). (Box 21, Folder 7-12)
  - F:AZW Miss Glenn Carpenter (Mays Lick KY). (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
  - F:AZZ Kay Goeggle (Ferriday LA). (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - F:BA Lou Santucci (Charlestown WV). (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - F:BC H.H. Muse (Safford AZ). (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - F:BD Minner Jane (Muse) Barnes (Union City TN). (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - F:BE 1987 Muse Reunion. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - F:BF R.H. Rogers (Troy TN). (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
  - F:BG Thomas Muse Orndorff. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - F:BH Mrs. Luci Ortner (Half Way MO). (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - F:BI Halford Muse (Troy TN). (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - F:BJ Richard Moore (Wiltshire England). (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - F:BK Betty Matthews (Shelbyville KY). (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - F:BL Robbie Ellen Muse Bryant (Tompkinsville KY). (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - F:BM Carl Franklin Muse (Charlottesville VA). (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - F:BN Vadis Burcham (Huntsville AL). (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - F:BO Virgil Griffin (Troy TN). (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - F:BP Mabel Pitts (Somerset KY). (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - F:BQ Sarah Simpson (Carthage NC). (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - F:BR Mary Jo Chamberlain (Roanoke VA). (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - F:BT Ivan Muse (Orem UT). (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - F:BV K.R. Forner (Grand Prarie TX). (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - F:BW Gordon Muse (Midlothian VA). (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - F:BW Mary M. Smith (Long Beach/Seal Beach CA). (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - F:BX March 1988 Manassas Trip. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - F:BY Carlton Maxwell Muse (Oriental NC). (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - F:BZ Richmond Archives. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - F:CA Col. George Muse Information. (Box 23, Folder 5-7)
  - F:CA Col. George Muse Information. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:CA Raymond Parks. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - F:CB Georgia Trip. (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - F:CB Georgia Trip. (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:CD Sharon Martin (Houston TX). (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - F:CE Jeanette Deaver (Fort Bragg CA). (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - F:CF J. Steven Muse (Felton PA). (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - F:CG Barbara Smith (Charlotte NC). (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - F:CG-2 Charles Edwin Muse (Fort Worth TX). (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - F:CH Troy Muse (Waynesville NC). (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - F:CI William Eugene Muse (Morrow GA). (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - F:CJ Raymond Edward Muse (Pinson TN). (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - F:CK Louise Umsted (Irving TX). (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - F:CL Sidney Ray Sandifer (Ringold LA). (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - F:CM Thomas E. Hamm Jr. (Stanford CA). (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - F:CN Lowell A. Muse (Oak Ridge TN). (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - F:CO Deborah Thomason (Dalton GA). (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - F:CP Dennis Wright (Gardena CA). (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - F:CQ Edward C. Muse (Dallas TX). (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - F:CR Charles James Muse (Cobb Island MD). (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - F:CS Maurice Stansell (Jackson TN). (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
  - F:CT Vesta Muse (Villa Rica GA). (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - F:CT Vesta Muse (Villa Rica GA). (Map-case G-14, Drawer 8)
  - F:CV Betty Jones (Globe AZ). (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - F:CW Collier A. Campbell (Texas City TX). (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - F:CW Scott Muse (Oklahoma City OK). (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - F:CX Joseph K. Muse (Decatur GA). (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - F:CY Merle McRoberts (Shirley IN). (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - F:CZ Dr. Pearson (Souldrop England). (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - F:DA Verna Bird (Duchesne UT). (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - F:DB Sandra Vlasin (Colorado City TX). (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - F:DC February 1989 England Trip. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - F:DE Roy Edward Muse (Gardena CA). (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - F:DF Stephen H. Muse (San Antonio TX). (Box 24, Folder 16-21)
  - F:DF Stephen H. Muse (San Antonio TX). (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - F:DF-2 1989 Southeastern Trip. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - F:DG Gwyn M. Dice (Woodbridge VA). (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - F:DH Jesse Robert Muse Jr. (Paris TN). (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - F:DI Nancy Lindeman (Navarre FL). (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - F:DJ Rita Litchfield (Federal Way WA). (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - F:DK David Hart (Houston TX). (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - F:DK-2 September 1989 Richmond Trip. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - F:DL 1989 Raleigh NC Archives. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - F:DM Carl Muse (Pascagoula MS). (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - F:DN Richard Taylor (Satellite Beach FL). (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - F:DO Bill and Stormy Turner (Hemphill TX). (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - F:DP Paul Reed (Salt Lake City UT). (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - F:DQ Jim D'Arc (Provo UT). (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - F:DR 1989 Salt Lake City Trip. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - F:DS Ellyn Fill (Marietta GA). (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - F:DT John Muse (Cypress CA). (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - F:DU Shirley Gray (Tullahoma TN). (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - F:DV George E. Taylor (Lawrence KS). (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - F:DW Sandra Benham (Alpharetta GA). (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - F:DX Elizabeth Hicks (Houston TX). (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
  - F:DX Elizabeth Hicks (Houston TX). (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - F:DX-2 Elizabeth Hicks (Houston TX). (Box 26, Folder 5)